The Inside Story. Filmed Over 20 Years.
Coldplay: A Head Full of Dreams is a music,
documentary film directed by Mat Whitecross.
An in-depth and intimate portrait of Coldplay's spectacular rise from the
backrooms of Camden pubs to selling out stadiums across the planet.
At the heart of the story is the band's unshakeable brotherhood
which has endured through many highs and lows.
Self, played by Guy Berryman.
Self, played by Jon Buckland.
Self, played by Will Champion.
Self, played by Chris Martin.
Self, played by Phil Harvey.
Self, played by Mat Whitecross.
Coldplay: A Head Full of Dreams is a music documentary directed by Mat Whitecross about
British band Coldplay, documenting their beginnings and rise to fame.
The film received a single-day release on 14 November 2018 in select cinemas
globally and was made available to stream on Amazon Video two days later.
It combines previously unseen footage along with performance
takes from the A Head Full of Dreams Tour.
It was met with generally mixed reviews upon release.
The film explores themes of rock band, cult music band,
music documentary, pop band, english musician.